instadp.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy - Instadp

_Effective date: 25 Dec 2018_

At instadp.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by instadp.com and how it is used.

## Information that we collect automatically on our Sites

Like many other Web sites, www.instadp.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

instadp.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.)

## Children’s Privacy

Our website does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

## Copyrighted Data & Search Results

We do not host any Instagram content. Our website is a search engine that helps you find users on Instagram.   
If you would like us to remove your account from search results please email us support@instadp.com

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information by using industry standard encryption. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) if you purchase a promotion, that information is encrypted and transmitted to stripe securely. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at support@instadp.com
